<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Collection</string>
    <!-- Strings used for fragments for navigation -->
    <string name="welcome_label">Welcome</string>
    <string name="initial_instructions_label">Stage 1 - Instructions</string>
    <string name="initial_data_collection_label">Stage 1 - Data Collection</string>
    <string name="exit_label">Submit &amp; Exit</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="begin">Begin</string>
    <string name="previous">Previous</string>
    <string name="confirm">Confirm</string>

    <!--  Motions  -->
    <string name="motion_arg_name">motion</string>
    <string name="circular_phone">CIRCULAR_PHONE</string>
    <string name="circular_head">CIRCULAR_HEAD</string>
    <string name="pointing_phone">POINTING_PHONE</string>
    <string name="pointing_head">POINTING_HEAD</string>
    <string name="translate_phone">TRANSLATE_PHONE</string>
    <string name="translate_head">TRANSLATE_HEAD</string>
    <string name="zooming_phone">ZOOMING_PHONE</string>
    <string name="zooming_head">ZOOMING_HEAD</string>
    <string name="peaking_phone">PEAKING_PHONE</string>
    <string name="peaking_head">PEAKING_HEAD</string>

    <!-- Consent -->
    <string name="final_consent">I understand that my likeness has been captured by the front facing camera and that I consent to it being used within the related research, and published alongside the research.</string>
    <string name="disclaimer">
        As should have been described in the briefing: data collected by this app will include your likeness, in particular your face, recorded by the front-facing camera.
        \n\nPlease do not over extend/strain yourself performing any motion. All motions performed should be done in such a way that they don\'t cause any discomfort.
        \nIf you need a break between the recordings please inform a researcher.
    </string>

    <!-- Instructions -->
    <string name="initial_instructions">
        This data collection app will have 12 Data collection stages. Each stage will be focused on performing a different type of motion that you will need to perform with either your head or the phone.
        \nYou should hold the phone in the same way you would use your phone to browse the internet or send/read messages.
        \n\nIn each stage you will be provided a video and written instructions describing what you need to do, within the app on the phone.
        \nIf you have any questions regarding what you need to do, please ask a researcher.
        \n\nOnce you\'re ready to start, inform the researcher that you\'re ready. They will then ask you to shake the phone, which will trigger a 3 second countdown for you to get ready.
        \nOnce the 3 second countdown is complete, the app will begin recording data (including images from the front facing camera).
        \nDuring this time uou should perform the requested motion ONCE, and press the \'Next\' button once complete. This will stop recording data, and take you to the next motion to perform.
        \nPlease let a researcher know when the countdown is complete.
        \n\nThis will be repeated until all the actions have been performed.
        \n\nIf you\'re ready, please let a researcher know and press the button on screen.
    </string>
    <string name="final_instructions">
        You have completed the data collection activities. Thank you.
        \n\nPlease reconfirm that you consent to the usage of the data collected within the study, in particular the capturing of your likeness via the front-facing camera, via the check-box below.
        \nThis is of course if you still consent to this. If you no longer consent, please inform the researcher/s and continue with the below.
    </string>
    <string name="exit_instructions">
        Please remove your earpiece and take off the hat/beanie. Ask for assistance if necessary.
        \nPlease either place the items provided back onto the table, or hand them back to a researcher.
        \nJoin the researcher to go over a debrief, wherein the researchers can answer any further questions, and further explain the use of the data and the goal of the research.
    </string>
    <string name="pointing_translate_phone_instructions">
        You should hold the phone in the same way you would use your phone to browse the internet or send/receive messages. You may support your arm if this is required.
        \n\nImagine a line drawn forward from the tip of your nose.
        \nWhile keeping your face still, move the phone such that the target on screen is aligned with the line drawn from your nose, then return the phone to the starting position.
        \nThe phone should not be rotated.
    </string>
    <string name="pointing_rotate_phone_instructions">
        You should hold the phone in the same way you would use your phone to browse the internet or send/receive messages. You may support your arm if this is required.
        \n\nImagine a line drawn forward from the tip of your nose.
        \nWhile keeping your face still, turn the phone such that your nose is aligned with the target on screen, then return the phone to the starting position.
        \nThe phone should remain in the same position.
    </string>
    <string name="pointing_rotate_head_instructions">
        You should hold the phone in the same way you would use your phone to browse the internet or send/receive messages. You may support your arm if this is required.
        \n\nImagine a line drawn forward from the tip of your nose.
        \nWhile keeping the phone still, turn your head such that your nose is aligned with the target on screen, then return your head to the starting position.
    </string>
    <string name="translate_phone_instructions">
        You should hold the phone in the same way you would use your phone to browse the internet or send/receive messages. You may support your arm if this is required.
        \n\nImagine a line drawn forward from the edges of your face.
        \nWhile keeping your head still, move the phone such that as much of the phone screen is not in-front of your face, whilst the target is aligned with one of your ears, your chine, or your forehead; whichever is requested. Then return the phone to the starting position.
    </string>
    <string name="circular_phone_instructions">
        You should hold the phone in the same way you would use your phone to browse the internet or send/receive messages. You may support your arm if this is required.
        \n\nWhile keeping your head still and the phone screen facing your face, move the phone in a little circle in the same direction as the targets. The phone should return to the starting point without needing to reverse the motion.
        \nImagine a line drawn forward from your nose, it should draw a circle on the screen.
    </string>
    <string name="circular_head_instructions">
        You should hold the phone in the same way you would use your phone to browse the internet or send/receive messages. You may support your arm if this is required.
        \n\nWhile keeping the phone still and the phone screen facing your face, move your head such that your nose moves in a little circle in the direction indicated. Your head should return to the starting point without needing to reverse the motion.
        \nImagine a line drawn forward from your nose, it should draw a circle.
    </string>
    <string name="zoom_phone_instructions">
        You should hold the phone in the same way you would use your phone to browse the internet or send/receive messages. You may support your arm if this is required.
        \n\nWhile keeping your head still and the phone screen facing your face, move the phone towards/away from your head (direction will be provided on screen). Then perform the opposite motion to return the phone to the starting position.
    </string>
    <string name="zoom_head_instructions">
        You should hold the phone in the same way you would use your phone to browse the internet or send/receive messages. You may support your arm if this is required.
        \n\nWhile keeping the phone still and the phone screen facing your face, move your head towards the phone. Then perform the opposite motion to return your head to the starting position.
        \n\nThe phone should remain in the same position (e.g. it should not be moved or rotated). Your nose should remain aligned to the target in the centre.
    </string>
    <string name="rotate_head_instructions">
        You should hold the phone in the same way you would use your phone to browse the internet or send/receive messages. You may support your arm if this is required.
        \n\nWhile keeping the phone still, turn your head such that your nose is pointing as far off-screen as is comfortable, turning in the direction of the target, then return your head to the starting position (such that nose is aligned with the centre of the screen).
        \n\nThe phone should remain in the same position (e.g. it should not be moved or rotated).
    </string>
    <string name="rotate_head_roll_instructions">
        You should hold the phone in the same way you would use your phone to browse the internet or send/receive messages. You may support your arm if this is required.
        \n\nWhile keeping the phone still, twist your head such that your nose is still pointing at the centre of the screen, but the top of your head is moving in the same direction as the targets, as far as is comfortable, then return your head to the starting position (the upright position facing the phone).
        \n\nThe phone should remain in the same position (e.g. it should not be moved or rotated).
    </string>
    <string name="rotate_phone_roll_instructions">
        You should hold the phone in the same way you would use your phone to browse the internet or send/receive messages. You may support your arm if this is required.
        \n\nWhile keeping your head still, twist the phone such that your nose is still pointing at the centre of the screen, but the top of the phone is moving in the same direction as the targets, as far as is comfortable, then return the phone to the starting position (the upright position facing the phone).
        \n\nYour head should remain in the same position (e.g. it should not be moved or rotated).
    </string>

    <string name="title_activity_data_collection">DataCollectionActivity</string>
    <string name="face_detection">FACE_DETECTION</string>
</resources>
